https://www.nybc.org/privacy-policy/

Home
Donate Blood
Where to Donate TodayDonor Center LocationsSchedule DonationPreciseMatch®Hemochromatosis Phlebotomy ProgramDonor AdvantageshaRED Blood DonationGroup Donations ProgramInfluencer ProgramAmbassador ProgramLegacy ProgramToolkit for SuccessHost a Drive / Register for shaREDCOVID-19 and Blood DonationConvalescent Plasma (CP)CP Donor Registration FormInformation for Health Care ProvidersInformation for Family and Patient AdvocatesConvalescent Plasma - Donor FAQConvalescent Plasma - FAQ for Health Care ProvidersBecome a DonorCan I donate blood?Donation ProcessDonation FAQsTypes of donationsWhy Donate?Need for African American and Latino/Hispanic Blood DonorsDonor ID CardsBlood FactsBe the Match ®Who We AreJoin the RegistryBecoming a DonorX
Products/Services
Blood ProductsCOVID Convalescent Plasma (CCP)Products for ResearchNational Cord Blood ProgramBloodHubCellular TherapyAbout Comprehensive Cell Solutions™ProductsServicesClinical DevelopmentCell Therapy Core FacilitiesLaboratory ServicesHLA LaboratoryImmunohematology and GenomicsNational Center for Blood Group GenomicsNYBC Blood Group GenomicsRedi-Kit Sample Shipping ProgramLaboratory FormsAssaysMedical ServicesHemophilia ServicesTransfusion Medicine ServicesClinical ServicesAutologous Platelet Rich Plasma/Bone Marrow ConcentrateCell SalvageClinical Force CommunityLipoprotein ApheresisTherapeutic Apheresis ServicesX
Research
About LFKRIAreas of ResearchLFKRI Seminar SeriesSummer Undergraduate Research ProgramResearch NewsInvestigatorsXiuli An, MD, PhDJeny R. Cursino dos Santos, PhDAsim K Debnath, PhDLanying Du, PhDDebra Kessler, RNCheryl Lobo, PhDLarry Luchsinger, PhDSara Lustigman, PhDAvital Mendelson, PhDVijay Nandi, MPHMohandas Narla, DScBruce Sachais, MD, PhDEric Senaldi, MDPatricia Shi, MDHong Van Tieu, MD, MSFrancesca Vinchi, PhDRona Weinberg, PhDConnie Westhoff, SBB, PhDKarina Yazdanbakhsh, PhDHui Zhong, PhDCore FacilitiesData Analytic ServicesElectron and Confocal MicroscopyFlow CytometryShared InstrumentationCOVID-19 Research RepositoryVaccine R&DCOVID-19 Disease ResearchAdditional ResourcesSickle Cell Information CenterOur Work in Sickle Cell Disease ResearchSickle Cell Disease - NYBCe PublicationsX
About Us
Contact UsLicenses, Permits & CertificationsDisaster Preparedness and Response Plan for HospitalsNYBC OverviewMission, Vision and ValuesNYBC Enterprises (NYBCe)LeadershipCommunity ReportNYBC HistoryVideo GalleryProfessional EducationTransfusion Medicine Fellowship ProgramEssentials of Transfusion Medicine - Webinar Series41st Annual Alexander S. Wiener LectureNYBCe at AABB 2020Work HereComprehensive BenefitsX
Support Us
Make a Financial ContributionHelp Us Fight COVID-19Contact Fund Development TeamHost a Blood DriveChairperson ToolkitApply to Host a DriveLittle Doctors Program®Bloodstock® Scholarship ProgramHigh School Scholarship ProgramVolunteer with NYBCVolunteer RequirementsBecoming a VolunteerVolunteer PositionsVolunteer Training Video: Canteen/EscortX
News
Media ContactX
COVID-19
Log InLog InDonorsBlood DonorsDonor Advantage ProgramChairperson PortalCustomersBloodHubLab FormsSearchDONATEDonate BloodDonate TimeDonate MoneyDonateHomeDonate BloodProducts/ServicesResearchAbout UsSupport UsNewsCOVID-19Privacy PolicyNew York Blood Center Web Site-Privacy StatementWelcome. Welcome to New York Blood Center's website, www.nybloodcenter.org. This web site is owned and operated by New York Blood Center, Inc., a New York not-for-profit corporation, with its headquarters in New York, NY ("NYBC"). This web site has been created to provide information about the activities, products and services of NYBC.Acknowledgement and Acceptance of NYBC's Privacy Statement. NYBC is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our web site and this Privacy Statement ("Statement") describes our commitment to protecting your privacy online, but NYBC wants to be sure you understand and accept that this commitment cannot guarantee privacy and confidentiality. Your use of the pages on this web site signifies that you have reviewed the terms of this Statement and accept its terms and conditions. The web site and our activities change frequently. As a result, we may make changes to the Statement at any time. If we modify the Statement in the future, we will publish such modifications on this web site and apply the modified practices to information collected online. Please review this Statement from time to time, and especially before you provide any personal identifying information.BY USING THIS WEB SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION AS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. YOU ALSO ACKNOWLEDGE THAT NYBC MAY PERIODICALLY CHANGE, MODIFY, ADD OR REMOVE OR OTHERWISE UPDATE THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ITS DISCRETION, WITHOUT PRIOR NOTIFICATION.Personal Identifying Information. We do not collect personal identifying information from anyone unless he/she provides this information knowingly and voluntarily. This information includes your e-mail address or other identifying information that you may provide if you choose to schedule a blood donation on line. We do not disclose or otherwise provide personal identifying information to any third party (other than third-party contractors assisting in the transmission of this information), unless such disclosure is required by law or applicable regulatory guidance.Other Information. Under certain circumstances, NYBC may use information collected on the web site (such as aggregated data, summary data, anonymously collected information) for business, marketing, surveys, research, advertising, etc., and may provide such information to third parties. Under no circumstances, however, will such information include personal identifying information, except as required by law or applicable regulatory guidance.Use of Personal Identifying Information by NYBC. There may be certain circumstances where NYBC will use personal identifying information obtained on the web site to contact you (for example, responses to your e-mail inquiries, recruiting for blood donations, etc.). If at any time you wish not to receive communications from us, you may indicate so by using the procedures described under "Contact Us" below.Social Media. NYBC makes use of certain social media channels (e.g., Facebook, Twitter) to which users post information and images knowingly and voluntarily. NYBC may, under certain circumstances, reproduce on its website such information or images posted by users to its social media accounts.Use by Children. NYBC is committed to protecting children. Most of the Information on this web site is intended for persons 18 years of age and older. NYBC will not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal identifying information from a minor under the age of 18, without obtaining prior consent from a person with parental responsibility (e.g., a parent or guardian) through direct off-line contact consistent with applicable legal requirements.Cookies. A "cookie" is a piece of information that a computer that hosts a web site may send to your computer (or web browser) when you access that web site. These bits of information allow the user to access the web site more rapidly in the future, but also allow the web site operator to gather information about site usage and potentially other information. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you can reject cookies using a procedure available in most browsers. NYBC provides no assurances or guarantees about the use of cookies on other web sites that you may visit as a result of information or links found on the NYBC web site.Security. NYBC uses a variety of security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, loss, misuse, alteration, destruction or disclosure. NYBC uses general, recognized security standards, including the use of Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") encryption when transmitting personal information over the Internet. Such transmissions are always subject to normal Internet security risks. Although NYBC has procedures in place to safeguard the information that we collect online, we cannot guarantee the transmission or disclosure of this information in a manner inconsistent with this Statement. No Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us.Links. This Privacy Statement applies only to this web site. This web site may contain references or links to other web sites not operated or controlled by NYBC. These third-party web sites are not covered by this Statement or the policies and procedures which NYBC applies. Therefore, if you follow a link posted here to third-party web sites, we provide no assurances or guarantees about these other web sites, including their ability to safeguard your personal information, and NYBC accepts no liability for links from this web site to others. NYBC can not endorse or guarantee any information you may find on links followed from NYBC's site. We suggest that you contact those sites directly for information on their privacy, security, data collection and distribution policies, as well as their content. NYBC is also not responsible for any third-party web sites that may contain links to this web site.Contact Us. If you have any questions or concerns about this web site, please contact usby e-mail: webmaster@nybloodcenter.orgIf you do not want NYBC to contact you in the future, please indicate so by sending an e-mail to webmaster@nybloodcenter.org to be removed from our lists. Last updated: May 17, 2013
